<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="question_0001_general">
        "What does this sign mean?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0002_general">
        "What must a driver do when this sign is accompanied by a white stop line on the road?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0003_general">
        "What must a driver do when this sign is NOT accompanied by a white stop line on the road?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0004_general">
        "This hand signal means the driver is.."
    </string>
    <string name="question_0005_general">
        "What should a driver do if another vehicle blocks their right of way at a junction?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0006_general">
        "A driver who is about to undertake a journey is upset or angry. What should they do?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0007_general">
        "When being overtaken and there is oncoming traffic, what should a driver do?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0008_general">
        "What effect does alcohol have on driver behaviour?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0009_general">
        "What effect does drinking alcohol have on a driver?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0010_general">
        "If a motorist or a motorcyclist is taking medication which may affect their driving, what should they do?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0011_general">
        "When driving along and wishing to use a hand-held mobile phone, what should a driver do?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0012_general">
        "What should drivers do if they approach road works and there is earth-moving machinery moving about?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0013_general">
        "What action should a driver take in a queue of traffic controlled by traffic lights?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0014_general">
        "What should the drivers do if they become drowsy while driving?"
    </string>
    <string name="question_0015_general">
        "When is it permissible to overtake another vehicle on the left hand side?"
    </string>
</resources>
