<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="answer_0001_general">
        "1. Stop, for school crossing ahead.\n"
        "2. Stop your vehicle.\n"
        "3. Other traffic must give way to you.\n"
        "4. Give way to traffic coming from your right.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Stop your vehicle."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0002_general">
        "1. Stop at the line.\n"
        "2. When you have passed the line.\n"
        "3. Only if there is traffic on the major road.\n"
        "4. No more than one car length past the line.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Stop at the line."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0003_general">
        "1. No more than one car length past the sign.\n"
        "2. Stop at the sign.\n"
        "3. Only if there is traffic at the junction.\n"
        "4. Only when having passed the sign.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Stop at the sign."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0004_general">
        "1. Slowing down.\n"
        "2. Turning right.\n"
        "3. Turning left.\n"
        "4. Going straight ahead.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Turning right."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0005_general">
        "1. Beep impatiently.\n"
        "2. Be patient and wait.\n"
        "3. Rev your engine.\n"
        "4. Try to squeeze around the blocking vehicle.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Be patient and wait."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0006_general">
        "1. Don't drive for the day.\n"
        "2. Try to calm down during the drive.\n"
        "3. Don't drive until they are calm.\n"
        "4. Drive, your emotions don't effect your driving ability.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Dont drive until they are calm."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0007_general">
        "1. Press hard on the brakes to create a big enough space in front of your vehicle.\n"
        "2. Speed up to make sure the overtaking vehicle can rejoin the left side of the road behind you again.\n"
        "3. Reduce speed and allow the overtaking vehicle to return to the left side of the road after completing the overtaking manoeuvre.\n"
        "4. Ignore what's happening in the opposite lane as it doesn't concern you.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Reduce speed and allow the overtaking vehicle to return to the left side of the road after completing the overtaking manoeuvre."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0008_general">
        "1. It slows down a driver’s reactions.\n"
        "2. It heightens a driver's reactions.\n"
        "3. It doesn't effect driver's reactions.\n"
        "4. It complements the driver's natural reactions.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: It slows down a driver’s reactions."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0009_general">
        "1. It wakens the driver up.\n"
        "2. It makes the driver more alert.\n"
        "3. It makes the driver a better driver.\n"
        "4. It makes the driver drowsy.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: It makes the driver drowsy."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0010_general">
        "1. Drive anyway, the drugs aren't illegal.\n"
        "2. Drive anyway because the drugs are prescribed.\n"
        "3. Seek medical advice in relation to driving.\n"
        "4. Ring a local pharmacy about your medication.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Seek medical advice in relation to driving."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0011_general">
        "1. Use an in car hands free intercom system.\n"
        "2. Use voice chat earphones so you're not holding the phone.\n"
        "3. Use the phone whenever you like during the journey.\n"
        "4. Stop at a safe location before using the phone. \n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Stop at a safe location before using the phone."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0012_general">
        "1. Reduce speed as there may be loose gravel or mud on the road.\n"
        "2. Speed up to get clear of the road works quicker.\n"
        "3. Maintain the normal speed limit for the road without exceptions.\n"
        "4. Stop to get a look at what's going on.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Reduce speed as there may be loose gravel or mud on the road."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0013_general">
        "1. A driver should be ready to speed away once the traffic lights go green or the queue clears.\n"
        "2. A driver should turn of their engine to avoid wasting fuel.\n"
        "3. A driver should try to navigate and get to the front of the queue.\n"
        "4. A driver should always maintain their position in the queue.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: A driver should always maintain their position in the queue."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0014_general">
        "1. Stop, take a break including a short walk if possible.\n"
        "2. Continue pushing on and stop at a local fuel station.\n"
        "3. Ignore your drowsiness and continue.\n"
        "4. Buy a stimulant like coffee or caffeine.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: Stop, take a break including a short walk if possible."
    </string>
    <string name="answer_0015_general">
        "1. When the vehicle in front is signalling to turn right.\n"
        "2. When the vehicle in front is signalling to turn left.\n"
        "3. When the vehicle in front is traveling straight.\n"
        "4. When the vehicle in front is reversing backwards.\n\n"
        "<b>Correct Answer</b>: When the vehicle in front is signalling to turn right."
    </string>

</resources>